If you're enrolled in Amazon brand registry,
you can enroll in Amazon Vine
to help boost sales, improve discoverability,
and gain valuable product insights
by tapping into the power of high quality Vine reviews.
You can launch a product with up to 30 reviews
by enrolling in Vine and making products
available exclusively to Vine Voices
as soon as you have an FBA listing and inbound inventory.
For products that are already live,
you can enroll them in Vine
as long as they have fewer than 30 reviews
on their product detail page.
Amazon shoppers rely on reviews to make purchase decisions.
When you invite approved Vine reviewers
to post reviews of these products,
you can help potential customers
make informed buying decisions.
Your products are reviewed
by an Amazon exclusive reviewer community known as Vine Voices,
which are highly engaged customers
who have been invited to participate
because of the trust they've earned
by writing helpful, unbiased reviews.
Voices are more likely to provide videos,
photos, and thorough product walkthroughs.
We connect your products with voices
who have purchased history and deep expertise
in your category,
which helps ensure high quality,
highly credible reviews.
To participate in the program,
you must be a professional seller.
Have a brand representative or reseller role
assigned to a registered brand in brand registry
and have an active fulfillment by Amazon FBA listing.
The Vine Dashboard shows preselected ASINs eligible
for the program.
But at a minimum, your FBA listing needs to have
an image and product description.
We recommend creating a strong listing
with thorough product details and high quality images
to equip Vine Voices with the information they need
to write high quality reviews.
Products that aren't eligible for Vine include bundled products,
products requiring additional purchases,
adult products, and digital products.
All products must also meet Amazon's general selling guidelines.
For more information,
review the restricted products help page in Seller Central.
Once you've confirmed your product is eligible,
access the Vine Dashboard in Seller Central.
Open the main menu,
hover over advertising and select Vine.
From the Vine landing page,
select Get Started with Amazon Vine
near the bottom of the page.
In the Vine Dashboard,
use the Eligible for Vine tab
to view recommended eligible ASINs.
You can also search for Eligible ASINs.
By default, all variations are pre-selected
displaying an estimated fee,
along with applicable discounts when eligible.
Select Edit Variations to adjust variations
included in enrollment.
Select Variations you want to include
and click Update Variations.
Check the boxes next to the ASINs
and variations you want to enroll.
Adjust the number of units up to 30 units maximum,
then click Enroll Selected.
To complete enrollment,
review the enrollment fee,
accept the terms and conditions,
and click Confirm Enrollment.
Remember, after you submit a product or product set,
you won't be able to edit a product variation
from the enrollment page.
However, you can add additional units
for up to 30 days after the enrollment.
The enrollment is submitted
and you return to the Vine page.
You can track your enrollment status,
the number of units claimed,
and the number of reviews left by reviewers
on the Vine dashboard.
Note that you may receive an error message
if you're not identified as a brand representative
or reseller.
The brand you represent isn't enrolled in brand registry,
or both.
You can cancel an enrollment only
when no units have been claimed.
If reviewers have claimed products,
you can stop enrollment to prevent additional products
from being claimed,
but reviews on already claimed products
may still be published.
To find reviews left by Vine reviewers
on a product detail page,
search for reviews tagged with the phrase
Vine Customer Review of Free Product.
For more information,
go to the Amazon Vine Help page in Seller Central.